意味がない！
In the fifth vote in the election
for the 13th chairman, 6) Botobai — 26
7) Mizaistom — 21
8) Morel — 20
9) Biscuit — 18
10) Saccho — 16
11) Linne — 15
12) Cutie — 10
13) Ging — 7
14) Sanbica — 3
15) Loupe, Bushidora — 0
Valid Votes: 633 (28 Absentees)
Turnout: 95.8% Pariston placed first.
ゴンは　どんなことをしても 俺が守る！
But since he didn't receive
the majority of the valid votes, 1) Pariston — 274 (41.4%)
2) Teradein — 77
3) Cheadle — 63
4) Leorio — 55
5) Ickshonpe — 28 those in the top eight must hold a runoff.
あぁ　やべぇ！ がぜん　やる気になって来た。 ヘヘっ グチャングチョンにしてやるよ！
Sin x And x Claw
) ゴンを…
Yes, hello?
)
Somehow, I managed to obtain a map.
どんなことをしても！ うぉ！
It has routes and destinations for all six airships.
うっ！
They seem to be on one of
the two remaining airships.
うわっ！
Want me to send a picture?
あの木が　どうしたの？
I don't think I'm so senile that someone
could tail me when I'm tailing another.
うわ。
As expected... You're late. Let's go!
すごい。 ウミテホタル。 汽水域にだけ生息して 今が繁殖期なんだ。
Tsubone's power, known as Rider's High, allows her to transform herself
into various different vehicles.
キレイ…。 でしょ？
However, the vehicles are
fueled by the rider's aura, so she cannot use her power alone.
グハっ！　うっ！
When we're above the clouds, no one can watch us from the ground,
no matter how strong the scope.
ハハハハ…！ ビビり過ぎだって　お前！
Yes! Well...
はぁ!? うわっ！ 一歩も動けねえじゃねぇか！
There's still time before either ship will land.
腰抜けたか？　ハハハ！
I'll help Hisoka out a bit longer.
ハハっ　ハハハ！　ハハっ　アハっ！ オホっ　アハハ…！
Nothing out of the ordinary here.
アハハ！　アハハ…！ うっ…。
The target has yet to appear.
あ　ダメだ　すげぇ気持ちいい。
We've lost all contact with Point C!
殺っちゃおうかな。
Nothing has happened at Point A.
あ　でも　楽しみてぇ　あ！
Should we tell them to send support? We can't assume that Point A is safe.
うわっ！
Illumi manipulates others with his needles.
はい。
It doesn't matter how many
amateurs we throw at him.
プレゼント。 世界で一番キレイな花。
We should warn the pros who are
going after the Needlemen.
あっ…。 これが？
Latun and Kenzaki aren't answering. What?
そのまま　じっとしてて。
The two airships they were
following are in close proximity.
その木の樹液が　ホタルの フェロモンと　そっくりで
Even if we can't predict the outcome, I don't
want to manipulate it through absenteeism.
集まって来るんだって。
Why don't we hire Association Hunters?
うれしい…。 ありがとう。
If we show that we're trying to carry on
the spirit of the Hunter Association, we could win some of the votes
that are defaulting to Pariston.
ホント？　よかった。
He's right. We should move immediately!
パームが本当に欲しいものを あげられないよ。
If everything works out,
the Association Hunters will be killed
私の欲しいものって？
and miss the next vote.
２人きりの時間。 えっ？
If I told him that, I'm sure Teradein would object.
うひゃひゃひゃひゃひゃ…！ うっ！
If we can't predict the outcome, we should force more absentees,
so it will be invalid.
キメラアントを倒せるくらい。
Teradein is too honest, and Bushidora can't plan well.
そのためには　もっともっと 修行しなくちゃダメなんだ。
Teradein-san has requested Hunters in
compliance with the Association's terms? Magnificent!
明後日　カイトが帰って来るけど 敵に操られてる状態らしくて
That's wonderful! Accept the request! Do the job! You don't need to be concerned about me.
元に戻すには　多分 術者と対決しなきゃいけない。
In fact, if there's no limit on the
number of Hunters we can send, spread the word and take everyone.
だから　せめて カイトを元に戻すまで…。
If you come across anything you want
to ask or tell me while on the job, feel free to contact me anytime.
できれば キメラアントを倒しきるまでは 修行に専念したいんだ。
If anything needs to be improved,
we can work it out.
それでも…　いい？
Yes, they make an excellent trio. I like them...
はぁ!?　何　言ってんの？
6th Election for the 13th Chairman
Total Number of Hunters: 661
ひょ！
The vote's invalid because the turnout was 91.2%. 1) Pariston — 272 (41.1%)
2) Teradein — 73
3) Cheadle — 66
4) Leorio — 58
5) Morel — 53
6) Mizaistom — 44
7) Botobai — 37
8) Ickshonpe — 0
Valid Votes: 603 (58 Absentees)
Turnout: 91.2% (Invalid)
ダメだ　たまんねえ！
What's going on?
うっ…。
Teradein!
)
Our members, the camera crew,
and the Association Hunters!
)
Even Bushidora!
イヤだ
Impossible!
うっ！　うぅ…。 ゴン…
Illumi must have hired dozens of strong soldiers!
俺が…
More like one.
守る。
Since we took flight, I haven't
felt anyone watching us.
くっ…　だって… 友達だもん。
Which means we really were being tailed before.
俺の大事な友達だもん！ あ　あぁ…　やめろよ　お前。 そんな顔されたら…。
Well, since we're this far from
the hospital, it should be fine. If anyone sees Alluka when we enter the hospital, Tsubone will say that Alluka's
power has been revealed, and she'll take us home immediately.
もう我慢できねえ…。 殺るよ　殺るよ　殺るよ。
But if I clear the area, that'll only
make it easier for Illumi to act.
) うるせぇよ…
Taking this airship to the
hospital would be difficult.
) お前なんかに… )
Gotoh's idea to drive a car straight
into the hospital may be best.
頭　残して　下は食って！ )
I can't reach Gotoh. Neither can I. Then I need you to tell Hishita and
the rest to send cars immediately
絶対に…　失いたくない！
to the following three locations. I understand.
) ゴンは…
We've lost the ground pursuit
by flying above the clouds.
)
We'll be fine until we're in the car.
俺の… )
After that, we have to pick the
best route to the hospital.
大切な…
Gon...
)
Hang in there.
大切な　友達だ！
Okay... Nice timing, Hishita.
うわ！
Since we had to loop around, it took longer.
ん？
But now we're sixty kilometers
from the hospital. They can't find us.
ん？
At once.
フッ　ハハハハ…。
What's wrong?
ハハハハ…。
There are people in front of the car.
やられた…。
Those... are Needlemen!
イルミの野郎 こんなもん差し込んでやがった。
Impossible! How? Following us should have been impossible!
俺の頭ん中にさ。
Was it the car? Did they follow the car? Hishita, hit the gas!
あっ？　何　言ってんだ？ イカれたか。
They're beyond help anyway! I can't do that, Master Killua.
てか　お前　今どうやって逃げた？
Not unless Master Illumi orders it.
いや　俺は見てる
Wh-What?!
そして　目の前から消えて あそこにいる
We're completely surrounded.
完全に目が覚めた。
Impossible...
いや　解放されたって感じかな。
How can he be here?
それだけのはずだ
Illumi...
それだけ…　あっ　あぁ…
How?!
これは　絶対に気のせいだ
It's impossible... Unless he knew which airship we were on!
俺が… 俺のほうがビビってるなんて
No, that's not right... Even if he knew which airship,
he couldn't be here.
他のアリにも言っといて。
We flew dozens of kilometers over the clouds.
「俺達に近づいたら 命ねえぞ」って。 うっ…。
He couldn't have followed us on the ground! Kil, you seem to be hiding something
from me about Alluka.
ふざけるな！
to get Hishita out of the car
and use it to escape? Or do I go back to the airship
and try to escape by air?
あっそ…。
If I were alone, those options would work.
じゃ　別にいいよ。
How did you know we were here? If I tell you, will you give me Alluka?
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
What do I do?
あっ！
I have to summon Something.
いない…。
It's me.
荷物も置きっ放しで…
Oh, it's Tsubone!
まさか　他にもアリが？
Your mother can see everything
そんな気配は　ない
that I see through this scope.
ってことは…！
She probably transmitted the
video to you, Master Illumi.
あっ…。
When the clouds cleared, I felt eyes on me again and realized the truth.
何してんだよ！
Ah, so you actually felt us watching... You're really something.
あぁ？　決まってるでしょ 罰を与えてるのよ。 私の気持ちを踏みにじった 罰！　罰！　罰！
Well, now you know the truth, but you can't remove that scope because
Mom ordered you to wear it.
ふざけんなよ！
Yes, you're completely right.
無理難題　ふっかけてんのは お前のほうだろ！ まっ　とにかく 無事でよかったけど…
Tsubone, give me the nail from your middle finger.
そりゃ　こっちのセリフだ　バカ 俺達の前から消えろ！
Yes, absolutely.
そのケガ　どうしたの？
Tsubone, give me the nail
from your ring finger.
ん？　あぁ　特訓だよ　文句あっか？
Yes, that's easy enough.
増やしてあげる！
Tsubone, I appreciate it.
無理だよ　あんたの包丁なんか 眠ってたって　よけられる。
Now, Master Killua...
殺ったと思ったのに…
Make your wish. Amane and I will take care of the rest.
いぃ… いぃ！ うわ！
Please allow me this opportunity to
make amends for impeding your mission.
待て！　殺す！
Are you going to do it? Fine...
うわ　うわ…　うわ！ ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…！
That means when you save Gon,
you'll follow the same process, right?
うっ　うっ　うっ…！ なっ!? 捕まえてみろよ　バカ！ 待て！
If you'd sacrifice those two to kill me, you won't have any problem sacrificing
a bunch of strangers to save Gon. Rule 5...
ダメだよ　キルア。
The same person can't make
two wishes in a row.
こんなことしたら 後で　もっと怒られちゃうよ。 あっ？　このまま　ばっくれて 会わねえに決まってんだろ。 ナックルには連絡しといてさ。 カイトとの再会は 別の場所にすりゃいいんだよ。
Would it be more fun to kill Alluka,
earning Killua's wrath, or more fun to spare Alluka and save
Gon, making Illumi my enemy?
死にてぇのか　おめぇはよ！
Tough call...
あの女が バトルタイプじゃないからって 油断してると 背後から　ぶっすり刺されんぞ！
If you say yes, I'll be happy to die.
ハハハ… そんなこと　されないってば。
Your inner mission will have succeeded.
あ！　おまっ…！ さっき　俺　あいつに包丁で…！ あり得ねえ　こいつ！
It's against the rules for family
members to kill one another, but the thing that will grant your wish...
うお！
Assuming there's a secret rule that
makes rule 5 not apply to Killua... If my death means no other family
will die, that's acceptable.
あれで逃げたつもり？ 甘いんだよ！
Killua will suffer for the rest of his life.
どこに行ったって分かるから！ アハハハ…！ あ　うぅ！
I will live in his heart forever.
うっ！　うぅ…！
Go ahead, then. I'm offering a deal, Kil...
いまいましい　クソガキキルアは どこ？
Alluka lives while Illumi dies, but I don't earn Killua's wrath.
いたいた　バカが！
So if Gon is healed, I neither gain nor lose anything.
ホテル？　駅側の…。 ガキが！　ガキガキガキ！ 邪魔ばっかしやがって！
In that case, I will kill Alluka to earn Killua's wrath, then take out Killua to earn Illumi's wrath.
こいつさえ　いなきゃ 全部うまく行くのに！
That is the best choice...
アッハハハ…！ どこまでだって　追いつめてって 消してやるわ！
Something, heal Tsubone's left hand.
うお！
'Kay.
ノ…　ノヴ様！
Hand. Hand.
あっ　はい　ホテルです 丸が３つ重なったマークの。
Tsubone, put out your left hand. Master Killua, but... Just do it.
[TEL]　ああ　たった今 あっちのほうから連絡があった。
Something is skilled at destroying,
but fixing isn't her forte.
あの…　予定では 明後日　到着では？ いや　予定通りだ。
When she's fixing, she must touch the target.
浮いた時間で あの２人を観察する。
But...
今のカイトと会わせても 耐えられるかどうかをな。 はぁ。
'Kay. Killua, pat my head!
そんなことよりもパーム。 は…　はい！
Of course, I will.
私に無断で 能力を使用しましたね。
That was amazing, Something.
不測の事態に備え 私の指示を待てと。 はい…。
Something is the one who calls me "Killua."
お前の血は 掛け替えのない貴重な源泉。
Healing someone is tiring,
so Something must sleep.
「掛け替えのない」？
But that's it.
私だけのために使え。 ノヴ様だけのために…
Something has never made a cruel
request after healing someone!
いいな？
Something is kinder than anyone.
は…　はい！
The one who's cursed is the one who wishes.
あ　やっぱり私には ノヴ様しかいない ところで何だ？　その格好は。
If you refer to Something as an object again, I won't consider you my brother anymore.
アハハ　アハハハ…。
Got it, Kil.
掛け替えのない… じゃあ　待ってもらえよ。
If you can heal Gon without any risk, that's terrific.
百歩譲って カイトを元に戻すまでさ。 それ　言った。 うぅ…。
But that doesn't change the fact
that Something is dangerous, and my questions remain unanswered.
ゴン＝フリークス　１２歳　Ｂ型 ほぼ　無理やり
Kil, you're still hiding something.
パーム＝シベリア　２２歳　Ａ型と 付き合うことになり
Such as how Milluki's rule 5 doesn't apply to you.
知らぬ間にフラれる
Until you tell me everything,
I won't let Alluka go.
チェっ　またこれか　３つ目だ。
would put needles in my head again.
ん？ おっ　シークレット！
Master Killua, I will take you to the hospital.
えっ？　そうなの？ ああ　それネットオークションでも かなりの高値がついてるぜ。 じゃあ　あげるよ。 いるかよ。
Captain Bushidora, of the Seirin Group, was killed in pursuit of the wicked Hunter
that we hoped to bring to justice. This confirms that demons are hiding among us!
何か　あったの？ ん？　別に。
However, I regret to say that the Seirin Group
ふん。
does not have the power to bring the
Hunter, or Hunters, to justice.
ジムで汗　流そうぜ。
Everyone! This is an urgent matter
うん！
that the Association must band
together to resolve at once!
どうだ？ いや　特には。
That is why our goal is to ensure
that voter turnout exceeds 95%, and that the winner has a majority!
大丈夫なようだな。
Thus, we are currently in negotiations
with Morel, who has strong ties with the former chairman's faction, in hopes
that he will be our new captain.
だが　もうしばらく　様子を見よう。 その間に　向こうも 片がつくだろう。 昨日の奴らより　動けるじゃん。 その間に　向こうも 片がつくだろう。
At the same time, we are prepared
to reveal the name, face, and abilities
昨日の奴らより　動けるじゃん。
of this demon to prevent further tragedy.
ゴンとキルアの精神状態を 観察していた同じ頃
If you agree with our ideals, please...
ん？
Oh, uh...
来たか。
I agree that I was fairly close
to the former chairman, and I participated in the Ant extermination.
フン。
It was determined that my support was required, given the nature of the operation.
何だ？　こいつ
Can't you adapt?
フッ　やるね。
And if you're in a hurry to end the election, you could tell your supporters to vote for Pariston!
おりゃ！
Though, I'd rather die than vote for him...
あっ…！ くっ…。
If you release his identity, you and a bunch of other fools will end up dying.
速い。
And don't use the "Seirin Group"
name when you're so weak!
ちょっとだけだけど。
The results of the seventh vote call
for a runoff between the top four.